Finding Aid for Frank Murphy Papers, 1908-1949
Bentley Historical Library
- Supreme Court Case Files, 1939-1948
  - 1941 Term
    - U.S. vs. N.E. Rosenblum Truck Lines, Inc.; U.S. vs. Margolies (# 52-53) (Reel 124)
    - Federal Land Bank of St. Paul vs. Bismarck Lumber Company, and John Gray, Tax Commissioner (# 76) (Reel 124)
    - Peter Young vs. U.S. (# 86) (Reel 124)
    - Great Northern Railway Company vs. U.S. (# 149) (Reel 124)
    - Walter Chaplinsky vs. State of New Hampshire (# 255) (Reel 124)
    - Goldstein, et. al. vs. U.S. (# 256) (Reel 124)
    - Rosco Jones vs. City of Opelika; Bowden and Sanders vs. City of Fort Smith, Ark.; Jobin vs. State of Arizona (# 280) (Reel 124)
    - Stonite Products Co. vs. Melvin Lloyd Co. and J.A. Zurn Mfg. Co. (# 321) (Reel 124)
    - Peter Lubetich vs. U.S. and I.C.C. (# 322) (Reel 124)
    - Seminole Nation vs. U.S. (# 348) (Reel 124)
    - U.S. (T.V.A.) vs. W.V.N. Powelson (# 500) (Reel 124)
    - Jacob vs. City of New York (# 589) (Reel 124)
    - M. Hampton Magruder vs. Washington, Baltimore, and Annapolis Realty Corp. (# 601) (Reel 124)
    - Harriett V. Pence vs. U.S. (# 665) (Reel 124)
    - Seminole Nation vs. U.S. (# 830) (Reel 124)
    - M. Hampton Magruder vs. Supplee (# 947) (Reel 124)
    - Other Cases:
      - (#1 & 3, 2, 10-13, 15-18) (Reel 124)
      - (# 20, 21, 23, 28, 29, 33-37) (Reel 124)
      - (# 42-46, 48, 49) (Reel 125)
      - (# 57, 58 & 59, 61, 63, 64, 67, 70, 78, 81, 91) (Reel 125)
      - (# 100, 110 & 267, 112, 124, 131 & 132, 139, 143, 151, 161, 179, 188) (Reel 125)
      - (# 197, 206, 252, 265 & 268, 272, 280, 286, 314, 318, 320) (Reel 125)
      - (# 508, 510, 527, 529, 535, 595, 602 & 603, 622, 648, 649) (Reel 125)
      - (# 711, 720, 723, 745, 755, 757, 759, 772, 774, 775, 782, 798, 799 & 800, 803, 814, 901, 910, 913, 966, 972, 990 1025 1036 1080) (Reel 125)
  - 1942 Term
    - Docket Book, 1 volume (Box 104)
    - William Schneiderman vs. U.S. (# 2) (Reel 125)
    - Warren-Bradshaw Drilling Co. vs. O.V. Hall (# 21) (Reel 125)
    - State Bank of Hardinsburg vs. Brown (# 23) (Reel 125)
    - Williams and Shaver vs. North Carolina (# 29) (Reel 125)
    - Riggs vs. del Drago (# 30) (Reel 125)
    - Helvering vs. Ohio Leather Co. et al. (# 40, 41, 42) (Reel 126)
    - Harry Pyle vs. State of Kansas (# 50) (Reel 126)
    - Warden of City Prison of Manhattan vs. U.S. (# 79) (Reel 126)
    - Choctaw Nation vs. U.S. and Chickasaw Nation (# 80) (Reel 126)
    - Fisher vs. Whiton (# 85) (Reel 126)
    - Mother Lode Coalition Mines Co. vs. Guy T. Helvering (# 94) (Reel 126)
    - Harrison vs. Northern Trust Co. and Mary E. Kaufman (# 103) (Reel 126)
    - Norvel H. Lilly vs. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. (# 124) (Reel 126)
    - Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Frances Perkins (# 142) (Reel 126)
    - Martin vs. City of Struthers, Ohio (# 238) (Reel 126)
    - Pacific Coast Dairy Co. vs. California Department of Agriculture (# 275) (Reel 126)
    - Overstreet, Brazle and L.L. Garvin vs. North Shore Corporation (# 284) (Reel 126)
    - Creek Nation, Seminole Nation vs. U.S. (# 321, 322) (Reel 126)
    - Leishman vs. Associated Wholesale Electric Co. (# 332) (Reel 126)
    - U.S. vs. Brooks-Callaway Co. (# 366) (Reel 126)
    - Penn Dairies, Inc. vs. Pennsylvania Milk Control Commission (# 399) (Reel 126)
    - N.B.C. et al. vs. U.S. (F.C.C.); C.B.S. vs. U.S. (F.C.C.) (# 554-555) (Reel 126)
    - Board of County Commissioners of the County of Creek, State of Oklahoma (# 556) (Reel 126)
    - West Virginia State Board of Education vs. Barnette, Stull and McClure (# 591) (Reel 126)
    - Oklahoma Tax Commission vs. U.S. (# 623, 624, 625) (Reel 127)
    - County of Mahnomen vs. U.S. (# 684) (Reel 127)
    - Virginia Electric and Power Co. vs. N.L.R.B. (# 709) (Reel 127)
    - McLeod vs. M.C. Threlkeld (# 787) (Reel 127)
    - Hirabayashi vs. U.S. (# 870, 871) (Reel 127)
    - Other Cases:
      - (# Ex parte Peru, 2, 7, 8, 20, 33, 61, 9 (Reel 127)
      - 10 orig., 10, 11 orig., 11-19 & 32, 23-29, 31, 43-46, 48, 59) (Reel 127)
      - (# 65, 67, 73, 74, 76-79, 81-82, 86, 87, 93, 97, 103, 124, 142, 171-173, 175, 178, 218, 229 & 329, 234, 238, 245, 246, 248, 254, 265, 268, 269, 275, 296, 299 & 329) (Reel 127)
      - (# 300, 303, 319, 320, 325, 327, 332, 336, 385, 387-388, 399, 420, 423, 429, 450 & 480-487 & 238, 458 & 453, 454, 460-461 & 72, 467, 473, 480-487, 280 & 314 & 966, 488, 495-496, 497, 520) (Reel 127)
      - (# 528, 529, 540, 551-554, 556, 558, 559, 573 & 619 & 1125582, 589, 659, 593, 606, 628, 640, 675, 684, 696, 698, 709, 722-723 & 783 & 849, 762, 766, 782, 787, 826-828, 826 & 837, 872, 840, 848, 855-856, 870-872, 876, 889, 903, 924-925, 934, 974, unnumbered notes) (Reel 127)
  - 1942 Special Term
    - "Saboteur Cases" (Reel 127)
  - 1943 Term
    - Docket Book, 1 volume (Box 105)
    - U.S. vs. Dotterweich (# 5) (Reel 127)
    - Carter vs. Kubler (# 18) (Reel 127)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue vs. Gooch Milling & Elevator Co. (# 53) (Reel 128)
    - U.S. vs. Gaskin (# 68) (Reel 128)
    - Thomson vs. U.S. (# 70) (Reel 128)
    - Falbo vs. U.S. (# 73) (Reel 128)
    - U.S. vs. Algernon Blair (# 75) (Reel 128)
    - U.S. vs. Hark and Yoffee (# 83) (Reel 128)
    - Tennant vs. Peoria and Pekin Union Railway Company (# 94) (Reel 128)
    - Prince vs. Massachusetts (# 98) (Reel 128)
    - U.S. vs. Seattle-First National Bank (# 267) (Reel 128)
    - Crites vs. Prudential Insurance Company (# 317) (Reel 128)
    - U.S. vs. Jasper White (# 366) (Reel 128)
    - U.S. vs. American Surety Company (# 381) (Reel 128)
    - Tennessee Coal, Iron & Railroad Company vs. Muscoda Local No. 123, etc. (# 409) (Reel 128)
    - Lyons vs. Oklahoma (# 433) (Reel 128)
    - Clifford F. MacEvoy Company...vs. U.S. for ...Calvin Tomkins Company (# 483) (Reel 128)
    - Follett vs. Town of McCormick, S.C. (# 486) (Reel 128)
    - Baumgartner vs. U.S. (# 493) (Reel 128)
    - Elmer Hartzell vs. U.S. (# 531) (Reel 128)
    - Mortensen vs. U.S. (# 559) (Reel 128)
    - Unpublished opinions (# 247, 302) (Reel 129)
    - Other Cases:
      - (# 1, 4, 5 orig., 9 orig., 19-26, 28-31, 33-40, 39 & 44, 42-47, 48, 51, 54-57) (Reel 129)
      - (# 62-65, 71, 84, 99, 105, 109, 112, 115, 117) (Reel 129)
      - (# 130-134, 142-146, 150, 151, 154, 155, 158, 159, 170, 183) (Reel 129)
      - (# 193, 195, 198, 200, 201, 209, 211, 215, 217, 226, 227, 232, 235, 247) (Reel 129)
      - (# 252, 262, 265, 276, 291, 302, 311-312, 316) (Reel 129)
      - (# 334, 336-339, 345, 349, 354, 362, 374-375, 384, 385, 388, 391, 392, 396-397, 398 & 423) (Reel 129)
      - (# 406, 417, 431, 433, 436, 463, 464, 472, 482, 486, 492, 493) (Reel 129)
      - (# 514-515, 521, 565, 569, 578, 587 & 635, 589, 592, 613, 620, 621 & 634, 628, 648, 649, 683, 716-717, 760, 767, 793, 880-882) (Reel 129)
  - 1944 Term
    - Docket Book, 1 volume (Box 105)
    - Korematsu vs. U.S. (# 22) [conference notes filed with: 1944 Term, Other cases, # 20] (Reel 129)
    - Smith vs. Davis (# 23) (Reel 129)
    - Walling vs. Helmerick & Payne, Inc. (# 27) (Reel 129)
    - Hoover & Allison Co. vs. Evatt, Tax Commissioner of Ohio (# 38) (Reel 129)
    - Screws et al. vs. U.S. (# 42) (Reel 129)
    - U.S. vs. Johnson (# 43) (Reel 129)
    - Steele vs. Louisville & Nashville Railroad Co. (# 45) (Reel 129)
    - Western Union Telegraph Co. vs. Leuroot (# 49) (Reel 129)
    - Dow Chemical Co. vs. Halliburton Oil Well Cementing Co. (# 50 & 61) (Reel 130)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue vs. Scottish American Investment Co., etc. (# 52-54 & 220-222) (Reel 130)
    - Associated Press vs. U.S., etc. (# 57, 58, 59) (Reel 130)
    - Northwestern Bands of Shoshone Indians vs. U.S. (# 63) (Reel 130)
    - U.S. vs. Waddill, Holland, & Flynn, Inc. (# 65) (Reel 130)
    - Ex parte Mitsuye Endo (# 70) [conference notes filed with: Term, Other cases, # 20], 1944 (Reel 130)
    - Williams and Hendrix vs. State of North Carolina (# 84) (Reel 130)
    - U.S. vs. Herman Rosenwasser (# 106) (Reel 130)
    - F.W. Fitch Co. vs. U.S. (# 181) (Reel 130)
    - Connecticut Light and Power Co. vs. Federal Power Commission (# 189) (Reel 130)
    - Fidelity-Philadelphia Trust Co. vs. Rothensies, etc. (# 263) (Reel 130)
    - Herget vs. Central National Bank & Trust Company of Peoria (# 322) (Reel 130)
    - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Locals 15 et al. vs. Eagle-Picher Mining and Smelting Co. (# 337) (Reel 130)
    - Malinski and Rudish vs. New York (# 367) (Reel 130)
    - Precision Instrument Manufacturing Co. vs. Automotive Maintenance Machinery Co. (# 377) (Reel 130)
    - American Power & Light Company vs. Securities and Exchange Commission (# 470 & 815) (Reel 130)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue Service vs. Lester Field (# 578) (Reel 130)
    - A.H. Phillips, Inc. vs. Walling (# 608) (Reel 130)
    - U.S. vs. Carmen Beach (# 620) (Reel 130)
    - Borden Co. vs. Borella (# 688) (Reel 131)
    - Goldstone and Bondy vs. U.S. (# 699) (Reel 131)
    - Allen Bradley Co. vs. Local Union No. 3, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers et al. (# 702) (Reel 131)
    - Jewell Ridge Coal Corporation vs. Local No. 6167 United Mine Workers of America (# 721) (Reel 131)
    - Harry Bridges vs. Wixon (Immigration and Naturalization Service) (# 788) (Reel 131)
    - 10 East 40th Street Building, Inc. vs. Charles Callus et al. (# 820) (Reel 131)
    - L.C. Akins vs. Texas (# 853) (Reel 131)
    - Charles Bowles (O.P.A. Administrator) vs. Seminole Rock and Sand Co. (# 914) (Reel 131)
    - L. Metcalfe Walling, Administrator of Wage and Hour Division, U.S. Dept. of Labor vs. Youngerman-Reynolds Hardwood Co., Inc. (# 955) (Reel 131)
    - L. Metcalfe Walling vs. Harnischfeger Corporation (# 956) (Reel 131)
    - Other cases:
      - (#-orig. [State of Georgia vs. Pennsylvania Railroad], 6, 13, 14, 20, 70, 21, 24 & 25, 26, 28 & 29) (Reel 131)
      - (# 31-33, 35-37, 40, 41, 46-48, 51) (Reel 131)
      - (# 55, 56, 62, 66 & 67, 71 & 485, 72, 74, 81, 83, 85, 86, 93 & 94) (Reel 131)
      - (# 115, 118, 180, 134, 126, 137, 148-150, 160, 180, 188, 182, 192, 205, 207, 212 & 259) (Reel 131)
      - (# 218, 226, 238, 259, 264, 265, 279, 287, 294-296, 307) (Reel 131)
      - (# 312, 321, 340, 342, 354, 367, 368, 370, 371, 379 & 380, 388, 391, 400, 410, 419, 421) (Reel 131)
      - (# 431, 445, 446, 448 & 449, 455, 462, 469, 470, 485, 486, 495, 507 & 508, 510 & 511, 514, 518, 520, 523-530) (Reel 131)
      - (# 534, 554, 559, 560 & 561, 570, 581, 588, 589, 593, 610, 613, 620, 629, 126, 630, 656, 684) (Reel 131)
      - (# 663, 666, 691, 710, 806, 811, 815, 833, 932, 953, 1016 &, 1017, 1189 & 1190) (Reel 131)
  - 1945 Term
    - Docket Book, 1 volume (Box 105)
    - North American Company vs. Securities and Exchange Commission (# 1) (Reel 131)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission vs. Engineers Public Service Company (# 2-3) (Reel 132)
    - Duncan vs. Kahanamoku (# 14-15) (Reel 132)
    - Chatwin vs. U.S., etc. (# 31-33) (Reel 132)
    - Better Business Bureau of Washington, D.C. vs. U.S. (# 52) (Reel 132)
    - Mabee et al. vs. White Plains Publishing Company (# 57) (Reel 132)
    - Oklahoma Press Publishing Company vs. L. Metcalfe Walling, Administrator of the Wage and Hour Division, U.S. Dept. of Labor (# 61-63) (Reel 132)
    - Lillian Boehm vs. Commissioner of Internal Revenue (# 69) (Reel 132)
    - Miscellaneous. In the Matter of the Application of Masaharu Homma (# 93 & 818) (Reel 132)
    - Julius Fisher vs. U.S. (# 122) (Reel 132)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue vs. J.N. Flowers (# 145) (Reel 132)
    - Frank Canizio vs. People of the State of New York (# 152) (Reel 132)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue vs. Wilcox (# 163) (Reel 132)
    - M. Kraus & Bros., Inc. vs. U.S. (# 198) (Reel 132)
    - Estep vs. U.S.; Smith vs. U.S. (# 292 & 66) (Reel 132)
    - Anderson vs. Mt. Clemens Pottery Company (# 342) (Reel 132)
    - Thiel vs. Southern Pacific Company (# 349) (Reel 132)
    - A.F. of L. vs. J. Tom Watson, Attorney General of Florida (# 448) (Reel 133)
    - Pennekamp and the Miami Herald Publishing Company vs. Florida (# 473) (Reel 133)
    - U.S. vs. Carbone et al. (# 474) (Reel 133)
    - Lavender vs. J.M. Kurn et al. (# 550) (Reel 133)
    - McAllister Lighterage Line, Inc. vs. U.S.A. and Interstate Commerce Commission (# 616) (Reel 133)
    - U.S. vs. Joseph A. Holpuck Company (# 696 & 697) (Reel 133)
    - Paul A. Porter, Adm., Office of Price Administration vs. Warner Holding Company (# 793) (Reel 133)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission vs. W.J. Howey Company (# 843) (Reel 133)
    - General Tomoyuki Yamashita (# 61 misc. & 672) (Reel 133)
    - Other Cases:
      - (# 5, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21,) (Reel 133)
      - (# 22, 23, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45) (Reel 133)
      - (# 46, 48 & 64, 49, 50, 51, 53, 54, 55, 56, 58) (Reel 133)
      - (# 60, 62, 65, 66 & 292, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77 & 83) (Reel 133)
      - (# 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95 & 103, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100) (Reel 133)
      - (# 101, 102, 104, 105, 106, 107, 108, 109, 110 & 111, 113, 114, 115 & 116, 117, 118, 119, 120, 121, 123, 124, 125) (Reel 133)
      - (# 126, 127, 128, 129, 130, 131, 133, 135 & 136, 137, 138, 139, 140, 141, 142, 143, 144, 146, 147, 148, 149, 150) (Reel 133)
      - (# 151, 152, 153, 154, 156, 158, 160, 161, 162, 163, 164-165, 167-168, 169, 170, 171-177, 178, 179, 181, 183, 184, 185) (Reel 134)
      - (# 186, 187, 188, 189-190, 191, 193, 194, 195, 197, 199, 202) (Reel 134)
      - (# 203, 209, 210, 211, 212, 213, 214, 215, 216, 219, 220, 221, 222, 223, 225) (Reel 134)
      - (# 229, 230, 231, 232, 233, 234, 235, 237, 238, 239, 240, 241-242, 243, 244, 245, 246, 247, 248, 250) (Reel 134)
      - (# 251, 254-255, 256, 257, 258, 259, 260, 261, 262, 263, 264, 265, 266, 268, 269, 272, 274, 275) (Reel 134)
      - (# 276, 278-282, 284, 285, 287, 288, 289, 292, 293, 294, 295, 296, 297, 298, 299, 300, 331, 332) (Reel 134)
      - (# 301, 302, 304, 305, 306, 307, 309, 435, 310, 311, 316, 317, 318, 319, 320, 321, 323, 324, 325 & 326, 327, 328 & 329, 330) (Reel 134)
      - (# 333, 334, 337, 338, 339, 340, 341, 343, 344, 345, 346, 347, 348, 350, 352, 353, 354, 355, 356-358, 359, 361, 362, 365, 366, 368, 369, 370) (Reel 134)
      - (# 371-372, 373, 377, 378, 381, 384, 385, 386, 387, 391, 392, 393, 394, 395, 396, 399, 400) (Reel 134)
      - (# 401, 402, 405, 406, 408, 410, 411, 412-413, 415, 418-419, 424-425, 428, 434, 435, 446, 457-458, 473, 484, 488) (Reel 134)
      - (# 505, 517, 518-519, 528-533, 540, 556, 572, 603, 605, 616, 496, 625, 749, 750, 769, 804) (Reel 134)
  - 1946 Term
    - Individual Opinion Assignment Sheets (Reel 134)
    - Docket Book, Cases # 1-1000 (Reel 134)
    - Docket Book, Cases # 1001-1508 (Reel 135)
    - American Power and Light Company vs. Securities and Exchange Commission (# 4 & 5) (Reel 135)
    - Cleveland vs. U.S., etc. (# 12-19) (Reel 135)
    - Bruce's Juices, Inc. vs. American Can Company (# 27) (Reel 135)
    - George Harris vs. U.S. (# 34) (Reel 135)
    - Carter vs. State of Illinois (# 36) (Reel 135)
    - Hickman vs. Taylor (# 47) (Reel 136)
    - Haupt vs. U.S. (# 49) (Reel 136)
    - Arch R. Everson vs. Board of Education of the Township of Ewing, et al. (# 52) (Reel 136)
    - National Labor Relations Board vs. A.J. Tower Company (# 60) (Reel 136)
    - Order of Railway Conductors vs. O.E. Swan, et al., etc. (# 63 & 64) (Reel 136)
    - Walling, Adm. of the Wage and Hour Division, U.S. Dept. of Labor vs. Halliburton Oil Well Cementing Company (# 74) (Reel 136)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission vs. Chenery Corporation, et al. (# 81 & 82) (Reel 136)
    - U.S. vs. N.Y. Rayon Importing Co., Inc. (#2), et al. (# 94 & 96) (Reel 136)
    - Admiral Dewey Adamson vs. California (# 102) (Reel 136)
    - U.S. vs. Thayer-West Point Hotel Company (# 106) (Reel 136)
    - Confederated Bands of Ute Indians vs. U.S. (# 141) (Reel 136)
    - State of Louisiana, ex rel. Willie Francis vs. E.L. Resweber (# 142) (Reel 136)
    - Craig, et al. vs. Harvey (# 241) (Reel 136)
    - Frank A. Cardillo (U.S. Employees' Compensation Commission) vs. Liberty Mutual Insurance Company, et al. (# 265) (Reel 136)
    - Industrial Commission of Wisconsin, et al. vs. E.E. McCartin and Continental Casualty Company (# 270) (Reel 136)
    - United States National Bank in Johnston, etc. vs. Chase National Bank of New York (# 371) (Reel 137)
    - Joseph S. Fay vs. People of the State of New York, etc. (# 377 & 452) (Reel 137)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, etc. vs. George G. Remund (# 417) (Reel 137)
    - National Labor Relations Board vs. Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation (# 418) (Reel 137)
    - National Labor Relations Board vs. E.C. Atkins and Company (# 419) (Reel 137)
    - Ayrshire Collieries Corporation, et al. vs. U.S., Interstate Commerce Commission, et al. (# 467) (Reel 137)
    - Rescue Army vs. Municipal Court of the City of Los Angeles (# 574) (Reel 137)
    - U.S. vs. Michael Walsh (# 718) (Reel 137)
    - U.S. vs. United Mine Workers of America (# 759, 760, 781, 782, 811) (Reel 137)
    - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen vs. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company (# 970) (Reel 137)
    - U.S. vs. Yellow Cab Company, et al. (# 1035) (Reel 138)
    - Other Cases:
      - (# 3, 6-10, 11, 12-19, 37, 40) (Reel 138)
      - (# 10 orig., 25, 28, 29 & 30, 31, 32, 33, 35, 51, 53, 54, 55 & 76, 56 & 57, 102, 453, 58 & 59, 65, 61, 62, 66, 68, 69, 70 & 71, 74, 564, 497, 207, 72, 77 & 78, 79, 93, 85, 80, 83, 88, 89, 90, 91, 574, 371, 92, 140, 690, 97 & 98, 229, 148-155, 209, 265) (Reel 138)
      - (# 184, 384, 253-256, 312, 270, 335-336, 343-345, 543, 377-452, 400, 393, 67, 578, 404, 417, 281, 367, 428, 430, 443, 461, 432, 470-472, 444, 447, 474, 498, 585, 512 & 583, 514, 562, 235, 385, 564, 593, 656, 715, 718, 464, 606, 682, 625, 626, 636, 656, 658, 674 & 675, 850, 680, 731 & 732, 687, 690, 704, 733, 954, 970, 840 & 535, 512, 847, 862, 934, 405, 945-947, 540, 954) (Reel 138)
  - 1947 Term
    - James F. Morris vs. William R. McComb, Adm., Wage and Hour Division, U.S. Dept. of Labor (# 7) (Reel 138)
    - Central Greyhound Lines, Inc. of New York vs. Carroll E. Mealey, etc. (# 14) (Reel 138)
    - Donald Wade vs. Nathan Mayo, State Prison Custodian of the State of Florida (# 40) (Reel 138)
    - Oyama vs. California (# 44) (Reel 138)
    - Cox vs. U.S.; Thompson vs. U.S.; Roisum vs. U.S. (# 66-68) (Reel 138)
    - Giles Kavanagh, Collector of Internal Revenue vs. J.H. Noble (# 70) (Reel 138)
    - H.C. Jones, Collector of Internal Revenue vs. Liberty Glass Company (# 71) (Reel 138)
    - McCollum vs. Board of Education (# 90) (Reel 138)
    - Albert Lee vs. Mississippi (# 91) (Reel 138)
    - Homer C. Price vs. James A. Johnston, Warden, Alcatraz Penitentiary (# 111) (Reel 138)
    - Harry B. Mitchell, etc., individually and as members of Civil Service Commission vs. Jack W. Cohen; etc. (# 130-131) (Reel 139)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue vs. Joseph Sunnen (# 227) (Reel 139)
    - Hurd vs. Hodge, et al.; etc. (# 290-291) (Reel 139)
    - Trupiano, etc. vs. U.S. (# 427) (Reel 139)
    - Comstock vs. Group of Institutional Investors, etc., et al.; etc. (# 451-454) (Reel 139)
    - Moore and Haughton vs. New York (# 485) (Reel 139)
    - Mary Morton West, Osage Indian vs. Oklahoma Tax Commission (# 489) (Reel 139)
    - Torao Takahashi vs. Fish and Game Commission (# 533) (Reel 139)
    - Samuel Taylor vs. State of Alabama (# 721) (Reel 139)
    - Other Cases:
      - (# 8, 13, 15, 824 (1946), 17, 51, 59, 69, 72-75, 78 & 88, 79-86, 87, 95, 105, 122, 139 & 371, 198, 223, 224, 258, 270 & 428, 292-296, 373, 392, 397, 398, 400) (Reel 139)
      - (# 431, 432, 590, 655, 448, 461, 464, 486, 541, 542, 544, 583, 643, 674, 695 1116-1117, 1117-1118 unnumbered notes) (Reel 139)
  - 1948 Term
    - International Union, U.A.W., A.F. of L., Local 232 et al. vs. Wisconsin Employment Relations Board et al. (# 14-15) (Reel 139)
    - Wolf vs. Colorado (# 17-18) (Reel 139)
    - Fisher vs. Pace (# 45) (Reel 139)
    - National Labor Relations Board vs. Stowe Spinning Company et al. (# 46) (Reel 139)
    - Lawson vs. Suwanee Fruit & Steamship Company (# 56) (Reel 139)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue vs. Phipps (# 83) (Reel 140)
    - Nye & Nissen vs. U.S. (# 228) (Reel 140)
    - Gerhart Eisler vs U.S. (# 255) (Reel 140)
    - Daniel vs. Family Security Life Insurance Company et al. (# 297) (Reel 140)
    - Defense Supplies Corporation and Reconstruction Finance Corporation vs. Lawrence Warehouse Company et al. (# 298) (Reel 140)
    - California vs. Zook (# 355) (Reel 140)
    - Brooks vs. U.S. (# 388 & 389) (Reel 140)
    - Morgantown, West Virginia vs. Royal Insurance Company, Ltd. (# 396) (Reel 140)
    - Baxter Griffin vs. U.S. (# 417) (Reel 141)
    - Wade vs. Walter Hunter, Warden, Leavenworth Penitentiary (# 427) (Reel 141)
    - George W. Humphrey, Warden, Lewisburg Penitentiary vs. Bernard W. Smith (# 457) (Reel 141)
    - Christoffel vs. U.S. (# 528) (Reel 141)
    - Samuel Titto vs. New York (# 671) (Reel 141)
    - Emil Lustig vs. U.S. (# 1389) (Reel 141)
    - Other cases:
      - (# 51, 53, 63, 84, 88, 91, 92, 110, 128-126, 148, 197, 206 misc. & 233 misc. & 269 misc., 219, 228, 279, 239 misc., 240 misc.) (Reel 141)
      - (# 272, 292, 313, 327, 333, 355, 387, 396, 427, 437, 447, 448, 457, 464, 465, 500, Eisler vs. U.S.) (Reel 141)
  - Supreme Court collected materials, 1943-1949
    - Miscellaneous collected materials, 1943-1949 (Reel 141)
- Speech File, 1908-1947
  Speech File, 1908-1947 (Rolls 141-146, Boxes 75-77). This series is a collection of Frank Murphy's speeches and articles, both manuscript and printed, arranged chronologically.
  - Lists of speeches given, 1932-1942 (Reel 141)
  - Speeches, 1908; 1914; 1923; undated (Reel 141)
  - Opening of Recorder's Court and Ascension to the Bench by Frank Murphy, January 2, 1924 (Reel 141)
  - "Only the Helpless Hang" (Capital Punishment debate), January 31, 1927 (Reel 141)
  - Campaign address on behalf of Al Smith, 1928 undated (Reel 141)
  - Gristmill Club Dinner, Detroit-Leland Hotel. Subject: Famous Detroit Criminal Trials, March 20, 1929 (Reel 141)
  - Detroit Federation of Labor, April 1929 (Reel 141)
  - Campaign addresses, 1929 undated (Reel 141)
  - 1920s undated
    - Christianity and World War I (Reel 141)
    - Detroit Night Court (Reel 141)
    - Detroit Police Department (Reel 141)
    - University of Michigan (Reel 141)
    - Spiritual values (Reel 141)
    - Training of lawyers (Reel 141)
    - "Races Problem" (Reel 141)
    - Judicial Administration of the Criminal Law (Reel 141)
    - "The Citizen and Liberty" (Reel 141)
    - "Crime" (Reel 141)
    - "The Necessity for a Court Statistician" (Reel 141)
    - National Association of Probation Officers (Reel 141)
  - Fort Wayne Hotel, Detroit. Announcement of Mayoralty candidacy, August 19, 1930 (Reel 141)
  - Undated: Campaign address, August 1930 (Reel 141)
  - Undated: Campaign addresses, 1931 (Reel 141)
  - Detroit Street Railways, January 7, 1932 (Reel 141)
  - "The Procession of Forgotten Men", November 7, 1932 (Reel 141)
  - 1932 undated
    - Address at Naval Reserve Armory (Reel 141)
    - Detroit's fiscal crisis (8 addresses) (Reel 141)
    - Mayoralty addresses on Detroit problems (Reel 141)
    - "A Mayor's Interpretation of the Encyclical of Leo XIII, Forty Years After" (Reel 141)
  - Miscellaneous, January-June 1933 (Reel 141)
  - Miscellaneous, July-December 1933 (Reel 141)
  - Miscellaneous, January 1934-December 1936 (Reel 142)
  - Miscellaneous campaign addresses, 1936 undated (Reel 142)
  - Articles, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - Messages and press releases, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - Inaugural Address, Lansing, January 1, 1937 (Reel 142)